So, so,
hi, I'm Fr. 7 and I'm son, and I'm drinking your salt and currently
living in the Philippines. So, I have,
uh, experience in creating and VSC and VSN
with EI. So I'm going on,
what you drew to my personal space and my sample works in
this, in this,
uh, industry. So, there's the about me.
So it talks all about my experience,
my tools and, um, my,
a, a personal information.
So, there's my CV. And this is,
um, the, not updated yet,
but for you to have the information,
I work in the different companies. And e-commerce companies' brand.
In the span of one and a half year.
So, I work in the, in Singapore, Thailand,
U.S., Australia, uh, uh,
in local, in the Philippines. Of course,
I work in Canada. And all across of the,
So, uh, different countries in the world.
So, here's my, um, project. Project.
So, uh, it composes for, uh,
E1, E2, E3, and E4.
So, here's my winning edge, which is the E1.
So, for example, this one.
So, like this. Yes.
So, here in the hook I used the,
uh, the weird visuals because I do believe
that the viewers when they call they will be seen.
The, the judge, the visual, not the audio because it takes time to process.
Like, they will have a time,
it takes time to process like 0.5 seconds.
But at the first glance they will judge the visual if they're uhh.
Where is the watch? So,
uhh, of course in the hope, I'm making them weird and curiosity
grabbing. So,
yeah.
So, here is umm,
umm, I create a fast-face to maintain the retention of
the viewer. So, umm, I do believe that the retainer has,
guys, the attention span of the viewer is like eight seconds and
if we use the fast-face and,
uh, either with the add of sound effects and zoom in and zoom
out keyframe animation, I believe that the viewer,
is the attention that is maintained. So,
yeah, here is the, here in this time.
There's a problem,
a deterrent meaning the problem. Just the,
the past in their house. So, uh,
this time, uh, I introduced the, the,
the solution. So,
so, is a black and white tree and have the sound
effect to use. This represents the negativity or the wrong
doings of our nut to do.
So, yeah, I'm gonna send this.
This, too, because, ah, to maximize our time.
So, here, I'm here in this head.
Um, I have this,
um. Mm. I have this,
um, retention to maintain the viewer is,
uh, watch the whole video. And,
since I do have the experience in creating VTC,
they are pronged shomer ads. And it,
ah, I created a linear ads. And the strong meaning of the strong hook
and fast-facing is a way to believe that the viewer,
ah, the viewers is, ah, is converting into our buyers.
So, most of them, ah, 80% of this strategy is have
a- a result. So, ah, I'm looking forward to be part of your team.
Ah, if you want, you can do it, I'll just add it.
And, yeah. See you,
see you soon. That's where it-